<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="name">
        <item>Drake</item>
        <item>Tom Cruise</item>
        <item>Vin Diesel</item>
        <item>Kendrick Lamar</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="description">
        <item>Aubrey Drake Graham (born October 24, 1986) is a Canadian rapper, singer, songwriter, record producer,
            actor, and entrepreneur. Drake initially gained recognition as an actor on the teen drama television series
            Degrassi: The Next Generation in the early 2000s. Intent on pursuing a career as a rapper, he departed the
            series in 2007 following the release of his debut mixtape, Room for Improvement. He released two further
            independent projects, Comeback Season and So Far Gone, before signing to Lil Wayne\s Young Money Entertainment in June 2009</item>

        <item>Thomas Cruise Mapother IV (born July 3, 1962) is an American actor and producer. He started his career at age 19 in the film Endless
            Love (1981), before making his breakthrough in the comedy Risky Business (1983) and receiving widespread attention for starring in the
            action drama Top Gun (1986) as Lieutenant Pete "Maverick" Mitchell. After starring in The Color of Money (1986) and Cocktail (1988),
            Cruise starred opposite Dustin Hoffman in the Academy Award for Best Picture-winning drama Rain Man. For his role as anti-war activist
            Ron Kovic in the drama Born on the Fourth of July (1989), Cruise received the Golden Globe Award for Best Actor – Motion Picture Drama and
            his first Academy Award for Best Actor nomination. </item>

        <item>Mark Sinclair (born July 18, 1967), better known by his stage name Vin Diesel, is an American actor, producer, director and screenwriter.
            He is well known for his portrayals of Dominic Toretto in The Fast and the Furious film series, Richard B. Riddick in The Chronicles of
            Riddick series and Xander Cage in the xXx series. He is also a producer on sequels in these franchises, with his company One Race Films. </item>

        <item>Raised in Compton, California, Lamar embarked on his musical career as a teenager under the stage name K-Dot, releasing a mixtape that garnered
            local attention and led to his signing with indie record label Top Dawg Entertainment (TDE). He began to gain recognition in 2010, after his first
            retail release, Overly Dedicated. The following year, he independently released his first studio album, Section.80, which included his debut single,
            "HiiiPoWeR". </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="type">
        <item>Musician</item>
        <item>Movie Star</item>
        <item>Movie Star</item>
        <item>Musician</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="age">
        <item>32</item>
        <item>56</item>
        <item>51</item>
        <item>31</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="image">
        <item>drake</item>
        <item>tom_cruise</item>
        <item>vin_diesel</item>
        <item>kendrick_lamar</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>